TEFANNY I. YOUNG

Queenstown, New Zealand
(+64) 0226911007 | Tefannyoung@gmail.com
GitHub: TefannYoung | LinkedIn: Tefanny Imanil-Young

CAREER OBJECTIVE:

Experienced hospitality professional with a passion for problem-solving and attention to detail. I am excited to embark on a new career change and move to a junior web development role where I can apply my creative and technical skills to build clean, efficient, and user-friendly web applications. I am excited to learn new technologies and collaborate with a team to create innovative solutions that exceed client expectation.

EDUCATION:

ISTQB Certified Tester Foundation Level (CTFL) | Currently studying

Agile Project Management Foundation | APMG International Completed 2023

Code+, Full-Stack Developer Collection | Skillsoft Completed 2023

Graduate Diploma in Tourism & Hospitality Management | Queenstown Resort College Completed 2019

Bachelor of Science International Hospitality Management Specialize Cruise Line operation in Hotel services | Lyceum of the Philippine University Completed 2014

CORE SKILLS:

| Frontend | Backend | Framework | Source control | UI / UX |
|----------|------------|-----------|----------------|----------|
| HTML | JavaScript | Bootstrap | GitHub | Web flow |
| CSS | Python | Django | | Figma |

PROJECTS:

Project title: Wedding website

Brief description: I created a wedding website as a one-stop information guide for the guest.

Frameworks and languages used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

GitHub link: https://github.com/TefannYoung/TheYoungsWedding

Project title: My website portfolio

Brief description: My portfolio with attached document like my cv, certifications and projects.

Frameworks and languages used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript GitHub link: https://github.com/TefannYoung/My-Website-Portfolio

Project title: Countries and their Capitals

Brief description: I created a quiz game about Countries and Capitals.

Frameworks and languages used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

GitHub link: https://github.com/TefannYoung/Countries-and-their-Capitals

Project title: Portfolio Website

Brief description: I make my website portfolio mainly as my practice.

Frameworks and languages used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript GitHub link: https://github.com/TefannYoung/Trueself

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

Woolworths Group | Part-Time | September 2022 – Currently Retail Assistant

Queenstown, New Zealand

- Providing exceptional customer service
- Greeting customers/welcoming customers
- Assisting customers/serving customers in a timely manner
- Maintaining a clean shop floor
- Standing for long periods

The Rees Hotel, Luxury Apartments & Lakeside Residences | November 2018 - August 2022 Housekeeping/Self-Checker/Public Area Attendant

Queenstown, New Zealand

- Inspect rooms before they are available for sale
- Cleans occupied and vacant rooms
- Communicates the status of guestrooms to the Front Office Department
- Cleans and presses the proper's linens, towel and guest clothing
- Maintain soiled and clean inventory items
- Cleans the public area making sure it is neat and tidy
- Doing turndown service at night

Career Break | June 2016 - October 2018

During this period, I took a career break to take care of my family and while doing that I also pursued full-time study in housekeeping services and IELTS. I am proud of my dedication to my family and commitment to my education, which has helped me acquire a deeper understanding of the hospitality industry and further develop my skills and abilities.

Infinity Tower Suite | August 2015-September 2015 Housekeeping

Makati, Philippines

- Inspect rooms before they are available for sale
- Cleans occupied and vacant rooms
- Maintain soiled and clean inventory items

Bolton Hotel | August 2013-January 2014 Housekeeping

Wellington, New Zealand

- Wiped, dusted and polished furniture.
- Vacuumed carpets and deep clean stains.
- Change lines and restocked room supplies
- Washed windows and doors and inspected rooms
- Clean bathrooms, made beds, and removed trash